<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Wouter van Akkeren</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Wouter van Akkeren</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Funda Web Scraper</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/fundascraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/fundascraper/</guid>
      <description>School project for the course Online Data Collection and Management. This powerful tool scrapes all information from sold houses in a specific city, up to a year ago. The scraped data contains valuable information about for example selling durations. The code can be used for all cities in the Netherlands and can be extendeded to scrape information about houses that are currently for sale</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Funda</title>
      <link>https://example.com/projects/creations/fundascraper-kopie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 12:41:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/projects/creations/fundascraper-kopie/</guid>
      <description>The housing shortage in the Netherlands in the last few years has led to a serious housing crisis experienced today. Especially young people are encountering major difficulties in finding the right place for an affordable price. Also during the last political party elections, the housing crisis was a very much debated topic. For this reason, Team 2 realized the significance of creating a dataset that can give both house seekers and house sellers more insights into the housing market in the Netherlands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Results</title>
      <link>https://example.com/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/search/</guid>
      <description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;#34;HTML&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;JSON&amp;#34;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
